I I'm I'm just going to say I want
containers to die I really do I want
containers to die a horrible death the
fact that containers Docker containers
specifically are lxc and their Linux
container technology is limiting them
and I want micr VMS to win I want it to
be so easy to make a BM that can
integrate with the underlying GPU which
you can't do with a container not easily
because it's it's that's the whole
container problem so micr BMS should win
because if you use a micr BM then you
don't get get the problem not being able
to run a Docker container on Windows or
Mac or something like that you cannot
have containers Docker is containers
including pod Manish and all those
containers without Linux that means that
all the technologies that are running uh
to support containers on Windows and
other platforms have to have a micr BM
already they have to have a micr Linux
BM that then runs the container engine
that then can run Linux containers but
that gives up the ability to do anything
else with the VM if I could configure
the micro VM instead of using a VM
that's going to run you know it's going
to poorly run lxc containers because I'm
on Windows and this all came about
because uh we're actually looking at a
thread here that is is a problem because
GitHub run uh Windows Runners are are
hobbled and there's a few people here
that are making comments that are
somewhat naive because they're saying
the fact that Windows Runners don't have
feature priority with Linux Runners from
a company owned by m Microsoft is
baffling you know what it's not baffling
if you're not an idiot if you've been
following this at all you know that
Linux containers are a Linux technology
darker containers are Linux technology
they're not a Microsoft Technology they
can never ever run on Windows and to
make that comment means you don't
understand that you have to have Linux
there in the first place so the actual
fix for something like this is is you
know the PMS are all you know they're
kind of being overworked down here you
can read it for yourself and pause the
video but the point is that BMS are
better they're just better across the
board for everything and now that we
have firecracker and all the different
micr BM Technologies are emerging we're
starting to and you know the stuff that
that that ubun Ubuntu and canonical have
done uh canonical specifically has done
with like configuring microbiom or you
know this is way way better for our
architecture and our world in fact I
would love to see kubernetes die I
really would I would love to see
kubernetes die because it's a total
container technology and have some
technology come along to replace it and
I'm going to predict this is going to
happen this is going to happen within
the next 5 to 10 years there's going to
be a micr BM technology that totally
replaces Enterprise deployments on scale
with kubernetes and it's going to be
based on micr BMS watch mark my wordss
this is coming